Guide to the International Woodworkers of America Local 3-101 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- International Woodworkers of America Local 3-101 records, 1935-1979; 1937-1969; 3120-001; 10.51 cubic feet (21 boxes)
  - INTERNATIONAL WOODWORKERS OF AMERICA, LOCAL 3-101, 1940-1976; RECORDS SUBGROUP 1 (Box-folder 1/1-16/4)
    - STRIKES, 1961-1962; SERIES VIII (Box-folder 8/6-8/12)
      - General Correspondence, 1961-1962; Subseries A (Box-folder 8/6)
      - Minutes, 1961; Subseries B (Box-folder 8/7-8/8)
        - Minutes, August-September 1961 (Box-folder 8/7)
        - Minutes, October-November 1961 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Membership-Assorted Lists of Dues, Donations, Committees, and Picket Rosters., 1961; Subseries C (Box-folder 8/9)
      - Financial Records., 1962; Subseries D (Box-folder 8/10-8/11)
        - Vouchers, 1962 (Box-folder 8/10)
        - Vouchers, 1962 (Box-folder 8/11)
      - Assorted. Agreement, Wage Scale, Rules, Correspondence, and Ballots., 1961; Subseries E (Box-folder 8/12)
    - AGREEMENTS, 1940-1950, 1953-1956, 1959-1969; SERIES IX (Box-folder 8/13-9/2)
      - Agreements, 1940-1950 (Box-folder 8/13)
      - Agreements, 1953-1956 (Box-folder 9/1)
      - Agreements, 1959-1969 (Box-folder 9/2)
    - WAGE SCALES, 1953-1960, Undated; SERIES X (Box-folder 9/3)
    - RESOLUTIONS, circa 1941-1955; SERIES XI (Box-folder 9/4-9/12)
      - Resolutions, circa 1941 (Box-folder 9/4)
      - Resolutions, circa 1942 (Box-folder 9/5)
      - Resolutions, 1943 (Box-folder 9/6)
      - Resolutions, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 9/7)
      - Resolutions, 1945 (Box-folder 9/8)
      - Resolutions, 1946 (Box-folder 9/9)
      - Resolutions, 1947 (Box-folder 9/10)
      - Resolutions, 1950-1953 (Box-folder 9/11)
      - Resolutions, 1955 (Box-folder 9/12)
    - ELECTION RESULTS - Union Officers, 1946-1951, 1961; SERIES XII (Box-folder 9/13-9/16)
      - Election Results - Union Officers, 1946-1949 (Box-folder 9/13)
      - Election Results - Union Officers, 1951 (Box-folder 9/14)
      - Election Results - Union Officers - Ballots, 1961 (Box-folder 9/15)
      - Election Results - Union Officers - Tally Sheets, 1961 (Box-folder 9/16)
    - MEMBERSHIP, 1944-1949, 1961; SERIES XIII (Box-folder 9/17-9/18)
      - Dues Reports, 1944-1949 (Box-folder 9/17)
      - Registration Rolls, 1961-Undated (Box-folder 9/18)
    - FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1941-1976; SERIES XIV (Box-folder 10/1-10/23)
      - Local 2-101. Statements, 1941-1951; Subseries A (Box-folder 10/1-8)
        - Local 2-101. Statements, 1941 (Box-folder 10/1)
        - Local 2-101. Statements, 1942 (Box-folder 10/2)
        - Local 2-101. Statements, 1943 (Box-folder 10/3)
        - Local 2-101. Statements, 1944 (Box-folder 10/4)
        - Local 2-101. Statements, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 10/5)
        - Local 2-101. Statements, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 10/6)
        - Local 2-101. Statements, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 10/7)
        - Local 2-101. Statements, 1951 (Box-folder 10/8)
      - Local 23-101. Statements, 1952-1953; Subseries B (Box-folder 10/9)
      - Local 3-101. Statements, 1976; Subseries C (Box-folder 10/10)
      - Northern Washington District No. 2. Statements, 1947; Subseries D (Box-folder 10/11)
      - Western Washington District No. 23. Statements, 1954-1956; Subseries E (Box-folder 10/12-13)
        - Western Washington District No. 23. Statements, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 10/12)
        - Western Washington District No. 23. Statements, 1956 (Box-folder 10/13)
      - IWA International. Statements, 1947; Subseries F (Box-folder 10/14)
      - Local 3-75. Audit, 1959; Subseries G (Box-folder 10/15)
      - Local 2-101. Taxes, 1940-1953; Subseries H (Box-folder 10/16-22)
        - Local 2-101. Taxes, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 10/16)
        - Local 2-101. Taxes, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 10/17)
        - Local 2-101. Taxes, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 10/18)
        - Local 2-101. Taxes, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 10/19)
        - Local 2-101. Taxes, 1948-1950 (Box-folder 10/20)
        - Local 2-101. Taxes, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 10/21)
        - Local 2-101. Taxes, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 10/22)
      - Local 3-101. Taxes, 1974-1976; Subseries I (Box-folder 10/23)
    - COURT PAPERS, 1954, 1957, 1962; SERIES XV (Box-folder 10/24-11/7)
      - Balch Logging Company vs. Local 23-93, et. al., 1954 (Box-folder 10/24)
      - Crowell Lumber Company vs. Local 23-93, et. al., 1954 (Box-folder 10/25)
      - Davis vs. Local 23-93, et. al., 1954 (Box-folder 10/26)
      - Eclipse Lumber Company vs. Local 23-101, 1957 (Box-folder 10/27)
      - Everett (Port of) vs. Local 23-75, et. al., 1954 (Box-folder 11/1)
      - Holdridge and Wren Logging Company vs. Local 23-93, et. al., 1954 (Box-folder 11/2)
      - IWA. Local 3-101 vs. Weyerhaeuser Company, 1962 (Box-folder 11/3)
      - Jones and Anderson Logging Company vs. Local 23-93, et. al., 1954 (Box-folder 11/4)
      - Marney, Posey, and Ellison vs. Local 23-93, et. al., 1954 (Box-folder 11/5)
      - Scott Paper Company vs. Local 23-75, et. al., 1954 (Box-folder 11/6)
      - Weyerhaeuser Timber Company vs. Local 23-101, 1954 (Box-folder 11/7)
    - CASE FILES, 1942-1969; SERIES XVI (Box-folder 11/8-11/15)
      - Burnette (Elwood E.), 1955, 1957 (Box-folder 11/8)
      - Luoma (E.J.), Gallagher, 1948 (Box-folder 11/9)
      - U.S. National Labor Relations Board, 1954-1957 (Box-folder 11/10)
      - U.S. National Labor Relations Board, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 11/11)
      - U.S. National War Labor Board. West Coast Lumber Commission, 1942-1945 (Box-folder 11/12)
      - U.S. National War Labor Board. West Coast Lumber Commission, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 11/13)
      - U.S. National War Labor Board. West Coast Lumber Commission, 1945 (Box-folder 11/14)
      - Washington War Manpower Commission, 1944 (Box-folder 11/15)
    - REPORTS, 1945-1979; SERIES XVII (Box-folder 11/16-14/3)
      - IWA Reports, 1954-1979; Subseries A (Box-folder 11/16-13/3, 14/2-14/3)
        - Committee to Implement Resolution No. R.28. IWA, 1954 (Box-folder 11/16)
        - Directory of U.S. and Canadian Plywood and Veneer Producers, 1967 (Box-folder 11/17)
        - Supplement to the Interdepartmental Report on the Douglas Fir Lumber Industry. Prepared for a Commission Appointed by the National Defense Mediation Board, 1941 (Box-folder 11/18)
        - Economic Report. IWA. Convention Session on International Wage and Contract Policy, Vancouver, B.C., 1968 (Box-folder 11/19)
        - Economic Report. IWA. B.C. Interior Wage Conference, Kelowna, 1967 (Box-folder 11/20)
        - Economic Report for the Convention Session on International Wage and Contract Policy, 1973 (Box-folder 12/1)
        - Economic Report. IWA. Region I: Wage and Contract Conference, Vancouver, B.C., 1979 (Box-folder 12/2)
        - Economic Report. IWA. Region III: Convention, Portland, Oregon, 1972 (Box-folder 12/3)
        - Economic Report. IWA. Region IV: Convention, Minneapolis, 1967 (Box-folder 12/4)
        - Economic Report. IWA. Region IV: Wage Conference, Wausau, Wisconsin, 1968 (Box-folder 12/5)
        - Economic Report. IWA. Thirtyfirst International Convention St. Paul, Minnesota, 1979 (Box-folder 12/6)
        - Facts for Wage Negotiations. IWA, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 12/7)
        - International Tabulating Committee. IWA, 1955 (Box-folder 12/8)
        - National Association of Manufacturers Center for the Study of Union Monopoly Power, 1961 (Box-folder 12/9)
        - Northwest Regional Policy Committee Report to Broad Conference. IWA-CIO, CCL. Portland, 1955 (Box-folder 12/10)
        - Northwest Regional Policy Committee Report to Broad Conference. IWA. Portland, 1957 (Box-folder 12/11)
        - Resolution 26 Study. IWA, 1957 (Box-folder 13/1)
        - Statistical Data. Region III Convention, Portland, Oregon, 1963 (Box-folder 13/2)
        - Statistical Report. Region III Convention, Portland, Oregon, 1966 (Box-folder 13/3)
        - Second World Tripartite Technical Meeting of the Timber Industry (Forestry), I.L.O. Geneva., 1973 (Box-folder 14/2)
        - Summary Report of Northwest Lumber Industry and Related Data. IWA., 1958 (Box-folder 14/3)
        - Woodworkers of America, International. Local 2-101. Secretary, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 13/12)
        - Woodworkers of America, International. Plant Directory, 1967 (Box-folder 14/1)
      - Weyerhaeuser Monthly Safety Reports, November 1945-May 1952; Subseries B (Box-folder 13/4-13/11)
        - Weyerhaeuser Monthly Safety Report, November-December 1945 (Box-folder 13/4)
        - Weyerhaeuser Monthly Safety Report, January-June 1946 (Box-folder 13/5)
        - Weyerhaeuser Monthly Safety Report, July-December 1946 (Box-folder 13/6)
        - Weyerhaeuser Monthly Safety Report, January-July 1947 (Box-folder 13/7)
        - Weyerhaeuser Monthly Safety Report, August-December 1947 (Box-folder 13/8)
        - Weyerhaeuser Monthly Safety Report, 1948 (Box-folder 13/9)
        - Weyerhaeuser Monthly Safety Report, 1949 (Box-folder 13/10)
        - Weyerhaeuser Monthly Safety Report, January 1950-May 1952 (Box-folder 13/11)
    - SPEECHES AND WRITINGS, 1967; SERIES XVIII (Box-folder 14/4-14/5)
      - Douglas (T.C.) Address, 25th IWA Convention, Vancouver, B.C., 1967 (Box-folder 14/4)
      - Reuther (Walter) Address, 25th IWA Convention, Vancouver, B.C., 1967 (Box-folder 14/5)
    - CONFERENCES AND CONVENTIONS, 1943-1952; SERIES XIX (Box-folder 14/6-8)
      - CIO. California Council. 6th Annual "Support the President" Convention, Fresno, 1943 (Box-folder 14/6)
      - IWA. Northern Washington District Council. 10th, Everett, circa 1946 (Box-folder 14/7)
      - IWA. Northern Washington District Council No. 2 and Southern Washington District Council No. 3 Amalgamation Convention, Olympia, 1952 (Box-folder 14/8)
    - PHOTOGRAPHS, circa 1963-1937; SERIES XX (Box-folder 14/9)
    - CLIPPINGS, circa 1954-circa 1965; SERIES XXI (Box-folder 14/10)
    - NOTES, Undated; SERIES XXII (Box-folder 14/11)
    - EPHEMERA, 1940-1975; SERIES XXIII (Box-folder 14/12-14/16)
      - Union Training Program - Hypothetical Situations., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 14/12)
      - Union Training Program, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 14/13)
      - Union Training Program, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 14/14)
      - Material Relating to the Taft-Hartley Act, Assorted Cards, Assorted Signs, 1947, Undated (Box-folder 14/15)
      - Assorted Ephemera, 1940-1975 (Box-folder 14/16)
    - SUBJECT SERIES - Taft-Hartley, 1947-circa 1957; SERIES XXIV (Box-folder 15/1-15/3)
      - General Correspondence, 1947-1951 (Box-folder 15/1)
      - Assorted Reports, Correspondence, and Forms, 1947-1950 (Box-folder 15/2)
      - Assorted Affidavits, Petitions, Pamphlets, and Forms, 1947-circa 1957 (Box-folder 15/3)
    - BIG "W" MEDICAL AND HOSPITAL ASSOCIATION, circa 1952-1967; SERIES XXV (Box-folder 15/4-15/7)
      - Constitution, 1953 (Box-folder 15/4)
      - General Correspondence, 1953-1967 (Box-folder 15/5)
      - Minutes, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 15/6)
      - Assorted Lists, Financial Statements, Recommendations, and Statements, circa 1952-1965 (Box-folder 15/7)
    - BY-LAWS COMITTEE, circa 1941-1965; SERIES XXVI (Box-folder 15/8)
    - ECLIPSE MILL GRIEVANCE COMMITTEE - Minutes, 1945, 1947-1949; SERIES XXVII (Box-folder 15/9)
    - WEYERHAEUSER A. MILL SHOP COMMITTEES (Day Shift), 1943-1944; SERIES XXVIII (Box-folder 15/10)
    - WEYERHAEUSER B. MILL SHOP COMMITTEES, 1942-1949; SERIES XXIX (Box-folder 15/11-15/27)
      - Cleanup. Shop Committee. (Day Shift), circa 1943, 1946 (Box-folder 15/11)
      - Dry Kiln. Shop Committee. (Night Shift), 1943-1944, 1949, Undated (Box-folder 15/11)
      - Green Chains. Shop Committee. (Day Shift), 1943-1944, Undated (Box-folder 15/12)
      - Green Chains. Shop Committee. (Night Shift), 1948 (Box-folder 15/14)
      - Maintenance. Shop Committee. (Day and Night Shift), circa 1943-1949, Undated (Box-folder 15/15)
      - Planning Mill. Shop Committee. (Day Shift), 1943-1944 (Box-folder 15/16)
      - Planning Mill. Shop Committee. (Night Shift), 1948 (Box-folder 15/17)
      - River Track. Shop Committee. (Night Shift), 1944 (Box-folder 15/18)
      - Sawmill. Shop Committee. (Day Shift), circa 1943-circa 1944 (Box-folder 15/19)
      - Sawmill. Shop Committee. (Second Shift), circa 1943-circa 1944 (Box-folder 15/20)
      - Shipping. Shop Committee. (Day Shift), 1943-1949 (Box-folder 15/21)
      - Shipping. Shop Committee. (Second Shift), 1943 (Box-folder 15/22)
      - Silo. Day Shop Committee. (Day Shift), circa 1943-circa 1944 (Box-folder 15/23)
      - Stacker-Unstacker. Shop Committee (Day Shift)-Organization, General Correspondence, Minutes, and Application for Exemption from Attending Local Union Meetings., 1943-1945 (Box-folder 15/24)
      - Stacker-Unstacker. Shop Committee (Day Shift), 1942 (Box-folder 15/25)
      - Yard. Shop Committee. (Day Shift), 1943-1944 (Box-folder 15/26)
      - Yard. Shop Committee. (Night Shift), 1944 (Box-folder 15/27)
    - WEYERHAEUSER C. MILL SHOP COMMITTEES, circa 1943; SERIES XXX (Box-folder 15/28-15/29)
      - Day Shift, 1943, Undated (Box-folder 15/28)
      - Night Shift, 1943, Undated (Box-folder 15/29)
    - LARSEN (KARLY) DEFENSE COMMITTEE, 1953; SERIES XXXI (Box-folder 16/1-16/3)
      - General Correspondence, 1953 (Box-folder 16/1)
      - Minutes, 1953 (Box-folder 16/2)
      - "Facts on the Smith Act: Conspiracy to Wreck Trade Unions". Trial Transcript for United States vs. Huff et al. Member Lists, 1953 (Box-folder 16/3)
    - NELSON (PETE) DEFENSE COMMITTEE, 1949-1951; SERIES XXXII (Box-folder 16/4)
  - WOODWORKERS OF AMERICA, INTERNATIONAL. LOCAL 23-93 (Sultan), 1935-1957; RECORDS SUBGROUP 2 (Box-folder 16/5-18/7)
    - ORGANIZATION, Undated; SERIES I (Box-folder 16/5)
    - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE, 1936, 1937, Undated; SERIES II (Box-folder 16/6)
    - MINUTES, May 7, 1935-October 11, 1957; SERIES III (Box-folder 16/7-17/3)
      - Minutes, May 7-September 27 1935 (Box-folder 16/7)
      - Minutes, May 7-20 1935 ;; October 4 1935-May 24 1937 (Box-folder 16/8)
      - Minutes, May 28, 1937-September 13, 1937 (Box-folder 16/9)
      - Minutes, September 1, 1937-February 13, 1942 (Box-folder 16/10)
      - Minutes, September 3, 1948 (Box-folder 16/11)
      - Minutes, February 23, 1942-September 17, 1948 (Box-folder 16/12)
      - Minutes, October 8, 1948-November 23, 1951 (Box-folder 17/1)
      - Minutes, December 12, 1951-May 11, 1956 (Box-folder 17/2)
      - Minutes, April 13, 1956-October 11, 1957 (Box-folder 17/3)
    - MINUTES - EXECUTIVE BOARD, October 1, 1948-October 18, 1957; SERIES IV (Box-folder 17/4-17/11)
      - Minutes-Executive Board - Regional Meeting (Sultan), October 1, 1948-October 4, 1957; Subseries A (Box-folder 17/4, 17/8, 17/10)
        - Minutes-Executive Board - Regional Meeting (Sultan), October 1, 1948-May 7, 1954 (Box-folder 17/4)
        - Minutes-Executive Board - Regional Meeting (Sultan), June 4, 1954-May 4, 1956 (Box-folder 17/8)
        - Minutes-Executive Board - Regional Meeting (Sultan), April 6, 1956-October 4, 1957 (Box-folder 17/10)
      - Minutes-Executive Board - Branch Meetings (Skykomish, Granite, Monroe, Sultan, Granite Falls), November 9 1951-October 18 1957; Subseries B (Box-folder 17/5, 17/6-17/7, 17/9, 17/11)
        - Minutes-Executive Board - Branch Meetings (Skykomish, Granite, Monroe, Sultan, Granite Falls), November 9, 1951-August 29, 1952 (Box-folder 17/5)
        - Minutes-Executive Board - Branch Meetings (Skykomish, Granite, Monroe, Sultan, Granite Falls), March 14, 1952-January 8, 1953 (Box-folder 17/6)
        - Minutes-Executive Board - Branch Meetings (Skykomish, Granite, Monroe, Sultan, Granite Falls), February 2, 1954-October 11, 1954 (Box-folder 17/7)
        - Minutes-Executive Board - Branch Meetings (Skykomish, Granite, Monroe, Sultan, Granite Falls), November 10, 1954-May 18, 1956 (Box-folder 17/9)
        - Minutes-Executive Board - Branch Meetings (Skykomish, Granite, Monroe, Sultan, Granite Falls), May 25, 1956-October 18, 1957 (Box-folder 17/11)
    - NEGOTIATIONS, 1941; SERIES V (Box-folder 17/12)
    - AGREEMENTS, 1935-1936, Undated; SERIES VI (Box-folder 17/13)
    - FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1948-1957; SERIES VII (Box-folder 17/14)
    - ELECTION RESULTS - Union Officers, 1938-1941; SERIES VIII (Box-folder 17/15)
    - MEMBERSHIP-ATTENDANCE, October 26 1951-October 18 1957; SERIES IX (Box-folder 18/1-18/5)
      - Attendance, October 26 1951-June 27 1952 (Box-folder 18/1)
      - Attendance, July 11, 1952-March 13, 1952 (Box-folder 18/2)
      - Attendance, March 20, 1953-November 5 1954 (Box-folder 18/3)
      - Attendance, April 15 1955-August 1 1955 (Box-folder 18/4)
      - Attendance, June 8 1956-October 18 1957 (Box-folder 18/5)
    - COURT PAPERS, 1954-1955; SERIES X (Box-folder 18/6)
    - LISTS - Scabs - Greenwood Jobs, Local # 2570 (Lumber and Sawmill Workers. Omak.), Local # 2511 (Lumber and Sawmill Workers Union, Onalaska.), McCleary List., Undated; SERIES XI (Box-folder 18/7)
    - SAFETY COMMITTEE, 1947-1948, 1951; SERIES XII (Box-folder 18/8)
  - WOODWORKERS OF AMERICA, INTERNATIONAL. LOCAL 23-46 (Bellingham)., May 18 1951-August 19 1955; RECORDS SUBGROUP 3 (Box-folder 18/9-18/10)
    - MINUTES, May 18 1951-August 19 1955; SERIES I (Box-folder 18/9-18/10)
      - Minutes, May 18 1951-January 7 1955 (Box-folder 18/9)
      - Minutes, February 4 1955-August 19 1955 (Box-folder 18/10)
  - WOODWORKERS OF AMERICA, INTERNATIONAL. LOCAL 3-199 (Bellingham), 1955-1971; RECORDS SUBGROUP 4 (Box-folder 18/11-19/6)
    - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE, 1969, 1971; SERIES I (Box-folder 18/11)
    - MINUTES, July 10 1956-August 1971; SERIES II (Box-folder 18/12-19/3)
      - Minutes, July 10 1956-December 13 1960 (Box-folder 18/12)
      - Minutes, January 10 1961-July 14 1964 (Box-folder 19/1)
      - Minutes, September 8 1964-October 11 1966 (Box-folder 19/2)
      - Minutes, November 7 1966-August 1971 (Box-folder 19/3)
    - FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1955-1970; SERIES III (Box-folder 19/4-19/5)
      - Ledger, February 1955-August 1960 (Box-folder 19/4)
      - Audits, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 19/5)
    - LISTS - Death Benefit Fund, Auxiliary Fund, 1955; SERIES IV (Box-folder 19/6)
  - WOODWORKERS OF AMERICA, INTERNATIONAL. LOCAL 23-75 (Sedro Woolley), 1950-1959; RECORDS SUBGROUP 5 (Box-folder 19/7-19/10)
    - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE, 1952; SERIES I (Box-folder 19/7)
    - MINUTES - Regular and Executive Board, 1950-1959; SERIES II (Box-folder 19/8-9)
      - Regular and Executive Board, December 28 1950-October 9 1959 (Box-folder 19/8)
      - Executive Board, 1952 (Box-folder 19/9)
    - MISCELLANY - Supplemental Agreement, Resolution, Receipts, 1952, 1955; SERIES III (Box-folder 19/10)
  - WOODWORKERS OF AMERICA, INTERNATIONAL. LOCAL 2-54 (Anacortes), 1946-1958; RECORDS SUBGROUP 6 (Box-folder 19/11-19/12)
    - MINUTES, 1946-1950; SERIES I (Box-folder 19/11)
    - FINANCIAL RECORDS - Skagit Valley State Bank, 1952-1958; SERIES II (Box-folder 19/12)
  - SNOHOMISH COUNTY INDUSTRIAL UNION COUNCIL, 1936-circa 1964; RECORDS SUBGROUP 7 (Box-folder 20/1-21/10)
    - ORGANIZATION - Constitutions, Rules, and By Laws, 1941-1952; SERIES I (Box-folder 20/1)
    - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE-[Chronologically Ordered], 1940-1950; SERIES II (Box-folder 20/2-20/8)
      - General Correspondence, 1940-1941, 1944 (Box-folder 20/2)
      - General Correspondence, 1945 (Box-folder 20/3)
      - General Correspondence, 1946 (Box-folder 20/4)
      - General Correspondence, 1947 (Box-folder 20/5)
      - General Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 20/6)
      - General Correspondence, January 1950-February 1950 (Box-folder 20/7)
      - General Correspondence, March 1950-December 1950 (Box-folder 20/8)
    - MINUTES - Industrial Union Council. Snohomish County, 1939-1944; SERIES III (Box-folder 20/9-20/12)
      - Minutes - Industrial Union Council. Snohomish County, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 20/9)
      - Minutes - Industrial Union Council. Snohomish County, 1941 (Box-folder 20/10)
      - Minutes - Industrial Union Council. Snohomish County, 1942 (Box-folder 20/11)
      - Minutes - Industrial Union Council. Snohomish County, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 20/12)
    - MINUTES - IUC. Snohomish County. Political Action Committee, Undated; SERIES IV (Box-folder 20/13)
    - MINUTES - IUC. Washington. Executive Board, 1948-1950; SERIES V (Box-folder 20/14-20/15)
      - Minutes - IUC. Washington. Executive Board, 1948 (Box-folder 20/14)
      - Minutes - IUC. Washington. Executive Board, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 20/15)
    - MINUTES - Washington Commonwealth Federation. Executive Board, 1944; SERIES VI (Box-folder 20/16)
    - FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1939-1948; SERIES VII (Box-folder 20/17-20/19)
      - Hall Rentals, 1939-1941 (Box-folder 20/17)
      - Receipt Book, 1941-1945 (Box-folder 20/18)
      - Assorted Financial Documents, 1939-1948 (Box-folder 20/19)
    - RESOLUTIONS, 1946, 1949, Undated; SERIES VIII (Box-folder 21/1)
    - CONFERENCES AND CONVENTIONS - China and the Far East, San Francisco, 1946; SERIES IX (Box-folder 21/2)
    - LEGISLATION, 1945, Undated; SERIES X (Box-folder 21/3)
    - MEMBERSHIP, Undated; SERIES XI (Box-folder 21/4)
    - LEGAL DOCUMENTS, 1939-1940; SERIES XII (Box-folder 21/5)
    - LISTS, 1948, Undated; SERIES XIII (Box-folder 21/6)
    - CLIPPINGS, 1944-1946; SERIES XIV (Box-folder 21/7)
    - EPHEMERA - Constitutions, Precinct Maps, Pamphlets, and Petition, 1936-circa 1964; SERIES XV (Box-folder 21/8-21/10)
      - Constitutions, Precinct Maps, Pamphlets, and Petition, 1941-1947, Undated (Box-folder 21/8)
      - includes material relating to Harry Bridges, as well as state and national politics., 1936-circa 1964 (Box-folder 21/9)
      - Ephemera, Undated (Box-folder 21/10)
  - FISHERMEN AND ALLIED WORKERS OF AMERICA, INTERNATIONAL. CANNERY WORKERS. LOCAL 18 (Everett), 1937-1942; RECORDS SUBGROUP 8 (Box-folder 21/11-21/21)
    - ORGANIZATION, 1941-1942; SERIES I (Box-folder 21/11)
    - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE, 1942; SERIES II (Box-folder 21/12)
    - MINUTES, 1937-1942; SERIES III (Box-folder 21/13-21/14)
      - Minutes - United Fishermen's Union., October 1937-1942 (Box-folder 21/13)
      - Puget Sound District. Executive Council, with Cannery Workers 1938 (Box-folder 21/14)
    - AGREEMENTS, 1942; SERIES IV (Box-folder 21/15)
    - MEMBERSHIP, 1942-1943; SERIES V (Box-folder 21/16)
    - CONFERENCES AND CONVENTIONS, 1938, 1940; SERIES VI (Box-folder 21/17-21/21)
      - Federated Fisherman's Council of the Pacific. Second Annual Convention, San Francisco, 1938 (Box-folder 21/17)
      - Maritime Federation of the Pacific. Second All Alaska Convention, Juneau, 1940 (Box-folder 21/18)
      - Maritime Federation of the Pacific. Unity Convention, Ketchikan, 1938 (Box-folder 21/19)
      - United Fishermens' Union of the Pacific, First Annual Convention. San Pedro, California., 1938 (Box-folder 21/20)
      - United Fishermens' Union of the Pacific. Puget Sound District. Northwest Conference, Seattle, 1938 (Box-folder 21/21)
- International Woodworkers of America Local 3-101 records, 1940-1983; 3120-002; 7.97 cubic feet (6 boxes)
  Organizational features, minutes, wage scales, job descriptions, negotiations, agreements, grievances, and publications. A large portion of this accession deals with the activities of the Weyerhauster Standing Committee.
  Open to all users.
  Records stored offsite; advance notice required for use.
  Local 3-101, October 02, 1986
  - ORGANIZATIONAL FEATURES, 1955, 1959, 1967; SERIES I: (Box-folder 1/1-1/2)
    - Organizational Features, 1955, 1959 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Life Insurance Policy, 1967 (Box-folder 1/2)
  - MINUTES, 1946-1980; SERIES II (Box-folder 1/3-1/26)
    - Minutes, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Minutes, 1948-1950 (Box-folder 1/4)